boincstats.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy | BOINCstats/BAM!

### Privacy statement

_This information is only available in English!_

 **What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, fill out a form or participate in BOINC. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, phone number or Zip code. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

**What do we use your information for?**

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

* To personalize your experience   
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs) 

* To process transactions 

> Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

* To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature 

* To send periodic emails 

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions. 

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information. 

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. 

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell or trade to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. 

**Advertising and visitor tracking**

We use cookies to personalise content and ads, to provide social media features and to analyse our traffic. We also share information about your use of our site with our social media, advertising and analytics partners. 

**Third party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. 

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent. 

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account and going to the 'Edit Profile' page. 

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. 

**Online Privacy Policy Only**

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. 

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](http://www.freeprivacypolicy.com/). 

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on Sunday, March 11th, 2012. 

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Willy de Zutter   
boincstats.com   
The Netherlands   
webmaster@boincstats.com
